Organizational Charts Collection ua950.022
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
Organizational Charts Collection
1930-2017
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
ua950.022
85 Digital Files
Contains University-wide, divisional, and departmental organizational charts produced between 1930 and the present day.
Access
Access to this collection is unrestricted
Acquisition
Images in this collection were digitized from records in the collections of the University Archives and harvested from the websites of University divisions and departments.
Historical Note
Organizational charts in this collection span a wide range of the University's history, from the era of the State College for Teachers (1914-1959) through the various iterations of the State University, culminating in the present day University at Albany. The organization of the University changes frequently. Sometimes these changes have been minor: for example, slight changes in department names. Some of the changes have been more significant: the University has undergone major restructuring at various points in its history.
Scope and Contents
Each item in this collection is a PDF image of a different organizational chart. The level of organization varies. Many of the charts describe the overall organizational structure of the University, while some are specific to certain offices, divisions, or departments.
Arrangement
This collection has no series, and the contents are arranged chronologically.
organizational charts; Digital Files; UAlbany Reference Collections
- New York State College for Teachers, 1930 September
- New York State College for Teachers, 1934 January
- Student Affairs, 1965 November
- Dean for Administration, 1966 January
- Public Information Office, 1966 May
- Student Affairs, 1966 August
- Community Relations, 1966-1969
- University College, 1970 June
- Office of Undergraduate Admissions, 1970 August
- Office of the Vice President for Research and Dean of Graduate Studies, 1971 November
- University Libraries, 1973 June
- Student Affairs, 1973
- Office of Undergraduate Admissions, 1974
- State University of New York at Albany, 1985 August
- University at Albany, 1987 September
- Academic Affairs, 1988
- University at Albany, 1989 September
- Division of Student Affairs, 1989 September
- Division of Finance and Business, 1990 April
- University at Albany, 1990 September
- Division of University Advancement, 1991 September
- University at Albany, 1992 May
- Division of Finance and Business, 1992 September
- University at Albany Foundation, 1992
- University at Albany, 1993 August
- University at Albany, 1994 July
- Division of Finance and Business, 1996 April
- Division of University Advancement, 1996 April
- Division of Research and Graduate Studies, 1996 August
- University at Albany, 1996 September
- Division of Academic Affairs, 1996 October
- Division of Student Affairs, 1996 October
- Division of Finance And Business, 1997 January
- University at Albany, 1997 March
- Division of Finance and Business, 1997 December
- University at Albany, 1999 February
- University Libraries, 2004
- University at Albany, 2005 September
- University Libraries, 2006 February
- University at Albany, 2006 April
- Division of Academic Affairs, 2006 May
- University Libraries, 2006 November
- University at Albany, 2008 February
- Division of Academic Affairs, 2009 November
- University at Albany, 2010 January
- University Libraries, 2012 April
- Division of Academic Affairs, 2012 September
- Information Technology Services, 2012 September
- Division For Research, 2012 October
- University at Albany, 2013 January
- Division For Research, 2013 April
- Division For Research, 2013 June
- Division For Research, 2013 August
- Information Technology Services, 2013 October
- Division For Research, 2013 November
- College Of Arts And Sciences, 2013
- Division For Research, 2014 April
- Division For Research, 2014 June
- University at Albany, 2014 July
- Division For Research, 2014 August
- Division of Academic Affairs, 2014 October
- Division For Research, 2014 October
- Division For Research, 2015 January
- Information Technology Services, 2015 January
- Division of Academic Affairs, 2015 February
- University at Albany, 2015 April
- Information Technology Services, 2015 June
- University at Albany, 2015 July
- Division For Research, 2015 August
- Information Technology Services, 2015 August
- Division of Student Affairs, 2015 August
- College Of Arts And Sciences, 2015
- Division For Research, 2016 August
- Division For Research, 2016 November
- Division of Student Affairs, 2016 November
- Award Management Services, 2016 December
- Information Technology Services, 2016 December
- University Libraries, 2016 December
- College Of Arts And Sciences, 2016
- University at Albany, 2017 January
- Division of Academic Affairs, 2017 January
- Center For International Education And Global Strategy, 2017 January
- University at Albany, 2017 March
- University Libraries, 2017 March
- College Of Arts And Sciences, 2017
- University at Albany, 2018 May